alphatrade.com 2006-12-24

# AlphaTrade.com

**AlphaTrade.com** has created this **Privacy Statement** in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information such as name, home address, phone number and email address.

Correspondence from AlphaTrade.com shall be limited to disseminating log-in information, technical changes, or responding to member issues. AlphaTrade.com does not distribute unsolicited email messages. Members shall only receive "AlphaTrade.com" news releases as requested, or standard correspondence relating to ongoing corporate developments, site enhancements, and special events. This site contains links to other sites that AlphaTrade either has a working relationship with / subsidiary companies or partnerships. AlphaTrade.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

AlphaTrade.com has several partners in its operations that provide services to AlphaTrade. Those partners follow our guidelines and security procedures to protect your personal information. Our partners are not able to sell, trade or otherwise divulge your personal information separately from AlphaTrade and have taken steps to limit access to such. 

> **
> 
> AlphaTrade.com does NOT sell, rent, lease or otherwise distribute or make available in electronic, print or other media, any personal information relating to our members. 
> 
> **

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employee access to your information is controlled and limited to a need to know basis. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact the [Sales department](mailto:sales@alphatrade.com) or write to:

**AlphaTrade.com**   
Suite 1322 - 1111 West Georgia Street,  
Vancouver, B.C.   
Canada, V6E 4M3

Or email: [info@alphatrade.com](mailto:info@alphatrade.com)
